[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":151292,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":174496,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":11123,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":185624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":10349,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":195978,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2138,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":198121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4109,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":202233,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":4778,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":207017,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get yo ur resul t.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5184,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":212204,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1494,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":213703,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4466,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":218171,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1  = 2 beca use 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1536,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":219709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3343,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":223055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1598,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":224655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with t he first  number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2917,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":227574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1969,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":229547,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3194,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":232745,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1605,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":234353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2722,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":237076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1757,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":238835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4081,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":242919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1373,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":244294,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger,  you subt ract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":247207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1334,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":248544,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":36338,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":284888,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":108504,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":393396,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":11019,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":404421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1908,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":406334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":8913,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":415249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1128,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":416379,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is t he inver se of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3725,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":420108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1415,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":421525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":425237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3437,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":428678,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":6470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":435153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":13006,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":448163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":21418,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":469586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. < br /><br  /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":42242,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":511832,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":45272,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":557109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":3538,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":560653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10- 0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":37517,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":598173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":26167,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":624344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator u nder +<s ub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":76112,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":700461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":5176,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":705643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4902,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":710547,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1400,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":711953,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as acc urately  as possible.","rt":23483,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":735439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7894,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":743338,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1668,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":745010,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4527,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":749539,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3351,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":752896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7172,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":760071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4001,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":764076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4586,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":768667,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4145,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":772817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3824,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":776644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 because I can add 0 to every number to get itself","response_history":["0 BECAUSE","0 BECAUS","0 BECAU","0 BECA","0 BEC","0  BE","0 B ","0 because I can use 0 to ","0 because I can use 0 to","0 because I can use 0 t","0 because I can use 0 ","0 because I can use 0","0 because I can use ","0 because I can use","0 because I can us","0 because I can u","0 because I can add 0 to every number to get itself"],"rt":154849,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":931496,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":58990,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":990493,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":9017,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":999515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":14455,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1013976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because to get 0 then I need to add 6 to 3","response_history":["6 because if ","6 because if","6 because i","6 because ","6 because to get 0 then I need to add 6 to 3"],"rt":35583,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1049565,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes 2=2, 2+2=4, 2+2+2= 6, 2+2+2 +2+8, 2+2+2+2+2=1, 2+2+2+2+2+2=3, etc so I can generate every number 0-8 using 2","response_history":["yre","yr","yes b","yes 2, 2+2=4","yes 2=2, 2+2=4, 2+2+2+","yes 2=2, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=6, 2+2+22","yes 2=2, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=6, 2+2+2+2+8, 2+2+2+2+2=1, 2+2+2+2+2+2=2","yes 2=2, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=6, 2+2+2+2+8, 2+2+2+2+2=1, 2+2+2+2+2+2=3, etc so I can generate every number 1","yes 2=2, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=6, 2+2+2+2+8, 2+2+2+2+2=1, 2+2+2+2+2+2=3, etc so I can generate every number 0-8 using 2"],"rt":277927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1327497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, because I can't generate 2,4,6 or 8 using 3","response_history":["no, because I cab't ","no, because I cab't","no, because I cab'","no, because I cab","no, because I can't generate 2,4,6 or 8 using  3"],"rt":60037,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1387541,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because I can generate all numbers 0-8 using 5","response_history":["yes, because I can generate all numbers 0-8 using 5"],"rt":102454,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1490001,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because I can only generate 0,3 & 6; can't generate 1,2,4,5,7,8","response_history":["no because I can't ","no because I can't","no because I can'","no because I can only generate 0,3 & 6; can't generate 1,2,4,5,7,,","no because I can only  generate  0,3 & 6; can't generate 1,2,4,5,7,8"],"rt":95410,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1585419,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":10136,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1595561,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 + (n-1)","response_history":["1 + (n-1)"],"rt":65544,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1661108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What i s the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. 0 is reached whenever the operation results in the total being equal to n... x + (n-x) = x-x+n=n","response_history":["the ","the","th","t","inverse is teh ","inverse is teh","inverse is te","inverse is t","in","i","the inverse of","xthe inverse of","x the inverse of","x +the inverse of","x + the inverse of","x + (the inverse of","x + (nthe inverse of","x + (n-the inverse of","x + (n-xthe inverse of","x + (n-x)the inverse of","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number is the number that m","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number  is the number that m","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added sto ","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added  sto","x  + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added st","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added s","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so taht ","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so taht","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so tah","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so ta","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. ) ","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. )","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. 0 is reached by ","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. 0 is reached by","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added  to x so  that the result is 0. 0 is reached b","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. 0 is reached whenec","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. 0 is reached whenever the operation is ","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. 0 is reached whenever the operation is","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. 0 is reached whenever the operation i","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. 0 is reached whenever the operation results in the total being equal to n ","x + (n-x) the inverse of a number x is the number that must be added to x so that the result is 0. 0 is reached whenever the operation results in the total being equal to n... x + (n-x) = x-x+n=n"],"rt":254170,"trial_type":"question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1915283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"it seems that if there is no common denominator between x and n, then x is a generator","response_history":["it seems that if the ","it seems that if there is no common denomintaor ","it seems that if there is no common denomintaor","it seems that if there is no common denomintao","it seems that if there is no common denominta","it seems that if there is no common denomint","it seems that if there is no common denominator between x and n ","it seems that if there is no common denominator between x and n, then x is a generator"],"rt":112090,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2027380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":48686,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2076073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":39630,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2115709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False ","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":16984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2132698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterations of adding x to iteslf then you will get back to x without generating some of the numbers","response_history":["because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n ","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterations ","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few itera","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iter","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few ite","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then  after a  few it","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few i","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterationos ","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterationos","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterationo","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterations of addit ===","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterations of addit ==","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterations of addit =","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterations of addit ","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterations of addit","because if x is a multiple of a divisor of n, then after a few iterations of adding x to iteslf then you will get back to x without generating some of the numbers"],"rt":135171,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2267874,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":119726,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2387607,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"because if x is a generator, then its can't be a divisor of n so 2n will never be a divisor either","response_history":["because if x is a generator, then n-","because if x is a generator, then n","because if x is a generator, then it s in","b ecause if x is a generator, then its can't be a divisor of n so 2n will never be a divisor either"],"rt":200251,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2587864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":14983,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2602855,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2208,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2605067,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"54","response_history":["54"],"rt":3222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2608291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3726,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2612020,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"calculus - differential equations","response_history":["diff erential equations","cdifferential equations","cadifferential equations","caldifferential equations","calcdifferential equations","calcudifferential equations","calculdifferential equations","calculusdifferential equations","calculus differential equations","calculus -differential equations","calculus - differential equations"],"rt":28844,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2640871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently","1 - never heard of it"],"rt":32923,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2673799,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":6602,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2680406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":9301,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2689713,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood  the conc epts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3476,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2693194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":4228,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2697425,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2503,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2699932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What i s/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["Engk","English"],"rt":8208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2708143,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes","response_history":["yres","yre","yr","yes"],"rt":8420,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2716568,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"none","response_history":["none"],"rt":4882,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2721454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]